chnprice.com 2018-05-14

# aliexpress price history,aliexpress coupon,gearbest price history,gearbest coupon,lazada price history,lazada coupon

1\. We only collect anonymous information.   
We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address. We do not collect personally identifiable information about you. In other words, we do not collect information such as your name, address, phone number or email address. We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

2\. We don't share your personal data with other companies.   
We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies.

3\. No ad companies collect data through our service.   
We do not allow advertising companies to collect data through our service for ad targeting.

4\. You can ask privacy questions.   
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

5\. Analytics providers access data on our behalf   
Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user.

6\. We take steps to protect personal information   
We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

7\. Our full privacy policy includes more information.   
This privacy policy was last updated on 2014-07-15. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application.
